23andme is a company that if you don't
know it you said I don't know a lot
about it but my sister's used it you
send in a DNA sample and you get a lot
of information back on your hereditary
traits on other people that you are
related to she was able to find some
like third cousins in England that we
didn't know about and my grandmother was
able to explain to them stories about
their father that died when they were
really young anyway 23andme is a cool
service but it's a corporation that then
owns your DNA and your genetic
fingerprint really that's scary
that's why I haven't used it but there
are so many ways that I think as a
society we would benefit if we owned a
company like that one it wouldn't be
$250 to get it done so it'd be more
accessible you when you're adopted or
any other number of family secrets can't
come out unfortunately or fortunately
depending on your position but to see so
much possibility to find family and see
how we are all related and our big huge
humanity family life story if we have a
DNA reading company that we own and
therefore have control over what is done
and not done with the data so a pod
number 61 is a cooperatively owned
23andme